Hey, so we are going to learn
about CodeCommit,
but on July 25th, 2024,
AWS decided to discontinue this service.
So new customers cannot use the service,
and AWS is recommending you
to migrate to another Git solution
such as GitHub, GitLab, or a 3rd party git.
So you don't know what it is yet, but we'll see this soon.
But for this course, CodeCommit might still appear
at the exam for now.
And so therefore, I keep the CodeCommit lectures.
And every time I mention CodeCommit in the course,
and it could be in many different places,
assume that there's a GitHub integration
and don't get freaked out
because well, CodeCommit is just a GitHub replacement,
and that's all you need to know, as you will see very soon.
So that's it. You should be good for the course.
Don't worry if you see CodeCommit here and there,
it really doesn't matter.
But now you know everything about this unfortunate event.
All right, that's it.
I hope you liked it
and I will see you in the next lecture.